extendoffice.com 2019-04-22

# ExtendOffice - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy -- Effective Date: 18 December 2018

To reflect changes in data privacy laws, specifically the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) in the European Union, we've updated our Privacy Policy and added more details about what information we collect, why we collect it, and how you can exercise your privacy rights.

(" **ExtendOffice** " or " **we** ") respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this Privacy Policy. Your privacy is a priority at ExtendOffice.

This Privacy Policy describes the types of information, including Personal Data, that we collect from you when you visit this website <https://www.extendoffice.com/> ("Website") and use our products and services as described in this Privacy Policy, how we process that data, and your options to access or update your data.

**This policy applies to information we collect:**

through our Website (including our forums nd comment forms);

through the use of our products and services;

through email and other electronic messages between you and us (including our technical support services).

It does not apply to information collected by any third party, including through any application or content that may link to or be accessible from the Website or with our products.   
Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, do not to use our Website. By accessing or using our Website, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of these Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check this Privacy Policy periodically for updates. 

We go to great lengths to protect it. This Customer Privacy Policy covers why we collect your personal information, what information we collect, what we use it for and how we protect it.

**Why we collect your personal information?**

We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.

**What information do we collect? What do we use it for?**

We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.

**What information do we collect? What do we use it for?**

  * ExtendOffice takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.
  * ExtebdOffice uses secure server hosted by MyCommerce and other 3rd party credit card processors that encrypt the entire customer's personal information including name, address, credit card number credit card expiration date etc. before it is sent to us. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information.
  * You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure web browser like FireFox.

**MyCommerce**

MyCommerce is the software industry’s premier registration commerce provider. ExtendOffice uses MyCommerce to provide you with very secure and fast online purchase. For more information about the MyCommerce, please visit [here](http://cs.mycommerce.com/privacy-policy/mycommerce/mcus/).

**Cookies**

Our website uses cookies.

Insofar as those cookies are not strictly necessary for the provision of our website and services, we will ask you to consent to our use of cookies when you first visit our website.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.

Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.

Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

**We use cookies for the following purposes:**

1\. authentication - we use cookies to identify you when you visit our website and as you navigate our website (cookies used for this purpose are: _[identify cookies]_ );

2\. status - we use cookies to help us to determine if you are logged into our website (cookies used for this purpose are: _[identify cookies]_ );

3\. shopping cart - we use cookies to maintain the state of your shopping cart as you navigate our website (cookies used for this purpose are: _[identify cookies]_ );

4\. personalisation - we use cookies to store information about your preferences and to personalise our website for you (cookies used for this purpose are: _[identify cookies]_ );

5\. security - we use cookies as an element of the security measures used to protect user accounts, including preventing fraudulent use of login credentials, and to protect our website and services generally (cookies used for this purpose are: _[identify cookies]_ ); and

6\. analysis - we use cookies to help us to analyse the use and performance of our website and services (cookies used for this purpose are: _[identify cookies]_ ).

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of our website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google's privacy policy is available at: [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/.](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) The relevant cookies are: [identify cookies].

**Managing cookies**

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. The methods for doing so vary from browser to browser, and from version to version. You can however obtain up-to-date information about blocking and deleting cookies via these links:

(a) <https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en> (Chrome);

(b) <https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences> (Firefox);

(c) <http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/> (Opera);

(d) <https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies> (Internet Explorer);

(e) <https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411> (Safari); and

(f) <https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy> (Edge).

Blocking all cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites.

If you block cookies, you will not be able to use all the features on our website.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

ExtendOffice may amend this Privacy Policy from time-to-time. We will notify you of such amendments or changes by updating the “Effective Date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.

**ExtendOffice Contact Information**

If you would like to contact us with questions or comments concerning our Privacy Policy or if you feel your inquiry or request has not been addressed to your satisfaction, please contact ExtendOffice via email: [sales@extendoffice.com](mailto:sales@extendoffice.com?subject=About%20the%20privacy%20Policy).
